Contact

Uyo, Akwa ibom +2347065942606 (Mobile) austinobravo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/austineebogu-27818123b (LinkedIn) austinobravo.pythonanywhere.com/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Problem Solving Python (Programming Language) Web Content Writing

Certifications

Introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS

Bachelor of Engineering (Petroleum)

Nysc Certificate

Fundamentals of digital marketing

Austine Ebogu

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | PYTHON | DJANGO | REACT: in addendum possess problem solving abilities and good leadership skills.

Uyo, Akwa Ibom State, Nigeria

Summary

Recent graduate with excellent research, technical and problemsolving skills. Details oriented and able to learn new concepts quickly.

Dedicated individual interested in applying communication and interpersonal skills to any role.

Experienced in data entry, new technologies practice and handling money.

Can easily memorize product details and build customer relationships.

Experience

The RootHub Web Development Intern March 2022 - Present (1 year 3 months) Akwa Ibom State, Nigeria

- * Builts layouts based on User satsifsction using HTML5 and CSS3.
- * Implements improvements to boost site performance.
- * Tutored individuals and contemporary .

Moniepoint Inc. (Formerly TeamApt Inc.) Point of Sale Associate August 2022 - May 2023 (10 months)

Akwa Ibom State, Nigeria

Mace capital limited (Moniepoint mfb)

- * Calculated profits and losses per day interval.
- * Monitored what a customer prefers and how to keep them.
- * Built good customer/owner relationship.

National Youth Service Corps Platoon Leader

March 2022 - April 2022 (2 months)

Akwa Ibom, Nigeria

Nysc is a one-year compulsory service year as a duly certified Nigeria graduate and during it's camp session, I was made a platoon leader and managed different individuals of different tribes for regimented 21 days.

Rosie's garments Textile Worker January 2019 - December 2020 (2 years) Aba, Abia State, Nigeria

- * Assisted in inputting fabric roll thread to the machine.
- * Maintained the fabric machine in optimum capacity.
- * Did rigorous night shifts optimally.

Tonimas lube oil Lube oil Technician September 2017 - January 2018 (5 months) Aba, Abia State, Nigeria

- * Changed oil, transmission fluid and filters in machines.
- * Maintained safety regulation by removing and disposal of used oil.
- * Worked in the laboratory and understood Standard Organization principles (SON)

Education

Federal University of Technology Owerri
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Petroleum Technology/Technician · (January 2014 - December 2019)